In the last video, we discussed the Nifty trade,
where the price of soil was short-changing.
Now, we'll discuss a stock
and learn its secrets. This stock is
ICC
Log Ward General Insurance Company. It
can be seen on the chart that after January 9th, this
stock was trading at ₹1,281 and in this trading session, it has risen from
₹
1,073, meaning it has seen a healthy 16% increase. It's
also worth noting that in the 2023 budget, the
tax rate has been removed in the new tax result,
which is considered very negative for life insurance companies.
However, since this
stock is a general insurance company, not a
life insurance company, this move will have no effect on this stock.
Its closing price on Wednesday was ₹1,073.
According to our technical analysis, this
stock has changed its trend, and it should now
move higher. In every
video we make from here, we
discuss the trade and
try to identify the trend. Do
n't make your own decision to buy or sell anything, which you should
determine by yourself.  take it only